<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="tesla.landislaland.blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kaizen Glossary</title>
      <link>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/kaizen_glossary-2022-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/kaizen_glossary-2022-10-17/</guid>
      <description>Kaizen The concept of making continual product and process improvements, usually small and typically done by the entire workforce.
Continuous Improvement Process A series of sequential steps to forever analyze a product or a process and continue to increase the value added portion.
Lean Short for Lean Manufacturing System. The generic name given to the Toyota Production System.
5S A tool in the Lean Toolbox which focuses on workplace readiness. The 5 S&amp;rsquo;s stand for Sort, Set in order, Shine, Standardize, Sustain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take care of your workplace, 5S, and Kaizen Week</title>
      <link>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/take-care-of-your-workplace-5s-and-kaizen-week.-2022-08-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/take-care-of-your-workplace-5s-and-kaizen-week.-2022-08-07/</guid>
      <description>Kaizen Week, or Kaizen period is development procedure known as &amp;ldquo;take care of your workplace, 5S&amp;rdquo; was applied. The principle goal is for everyone in the company to achieve a more efficient and pleasant workplace in short period of time.
The 5S development consists of sort, set in order, shine, standardize, and sustain, working through each S in the order given.
For comparison purposes, photographs of the workplaces can be taken before the start and after completion of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Material-handling Equipment Used in Logistics and Distribution </title>
      <link>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/material-handling-equipmentdate-2022-07-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/material-handling-equipmentdate-2022-07-28/</guid>
      <description>1. Types of Material-handling Equipment Material-handling equipment is any hardware that is used to hold, position, weigh, transport, elevate, manipulate, or control the flow of raw materials, work in process, or finished goods.
This encompasses equipment that can range from the smallest manufacturing jig to the largest transfer truck used for transport.
The Material Handling and Management Society has divided material-handling equipment into the following categories:
 Conveyors Cranes, elevators, and hoists Positioning, weighing, and control equipment Industrial vehicles Motor vehicles Railroad vehicles Marine carriers Aircraft Containers and supports  The scope here is the discussion of material-handling equipment that applies to logistics and distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10 Principles of Material Handling</title>
      <link>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/the-10-principles-of-material-handling-2022-07-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/the-10-principles-of-material-handling-2022-07-28/</guid>
      <description>Fork truck, pallet jack, conveyor system, these are common things come to one&amp;rsquo;s mind when thinking of material handling. However, engineered material handling for a distribution system consists of much more than these simple examples. There are many essential factors to consider developing or modifying a logistics or distribution material-handling system, such as:
 The material being handled The required environment (cooler, freezer, etc.) The volume and speed of movement The type of facility required The type of equipment required &amp;hellip;  This is a summary of practical and useful guide to material-handling problems developed by the College-Industry Council on Material Handling Education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job, Career, and Life Principles of Mine</title>
      <link>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/job_career_life_principles-2022-07-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/job_career_life_principles-2022-07-20/</guid>
      <description>I put down some principles I (try to) follow on my job search, career development, and life exploration principles here, they are not in particular order.
  Job searching is not really about job searching. It is more about self-understanding, growing as a person, contributing to a team that I admire, and doing things that I respect.
  What feels like a big problem to us today is likely not a big deal in the grand scheme of things, it is hard to judge progress over short intervals, zooming out often puts things in perspective, ups and downs are an integral part of this life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Review of Continuous Improvement (Kaizen)</title>
      <link>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/a-simple-review-of-continuous-improvement-kaizen-2022-07-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>tesla.landislaland.blog/post/a-simple-review-of-continuous-improvement-kaizen-2022-07-13/</guid>
      <description>Continuous improvement, or Kaizen in Japanese, is based on a request from top management or a downstream manufacturing group, set up an improvement activity with participation of all employees and perpetually expand this program.
Why We Need Continuous Improvement Continuous improvement as it goes, is continuous
Improvement, without saying, is important for any organization and individual. Continuous improvement emphasizes continuous, which means it&amp;rsquo;s not a spot activity only for a certain period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
